<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    //Changelog Dialog

    <string name="changelog_text">
        &lt;b>For informations about the handling there is a help dialog (Menu -> More -> Help).&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>v 4.4&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>
        - fix: save screenshot&lt;br>
        - fix: saving entries containing an apostrophe&lt;br>
        - fix: option to restart app to apply swipe gesture&lt;br>
        - new: http basic authentication&lt;br>
        - improved: behavior of tab preview/behavior&lt;br>
    </string>


    //License Dialog

    <string name="about_title">Copyright © 2017  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        For more information visit the project site on github: https://github.com/scoute-dich/Browser&lt;br>&lt;br>

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.
    </string>


    //Help Dialog

    <string name="help_lists_title">&lt;b>The lists:&lt;/b></string>
    <string name="help_lists">Every list has a context menu, which you can reach by long pressing an item. Lists can be cleared with one click
        (Menu). You can sort lists by title or date. You can also search for entries in the lists.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Bookmark:&lt;/i> as always - save your favorite websites for a faster access. You can also set a bookmark as
        startpage by clicking the star. You can also set an empty page as startpage (Menu -> Empty page).&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>readLater:&lt;/i> here you can save websites if you want to read them anytime later, if they are not
        important enough to be a bookmark.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>History:&lt;/i> well, your browser history.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>passStorage:&lt;/i> here you can save (encrypted) login data from websites. If you want to delete entered
        login data on exit, you must enable \"clear cookies on exit\" in the settings.</string>

    <string name="help_toolbar_title">&lt;b>Toolbar:&lt;/b></string>
    <string name="help_toolbar">
        &lt;i>Swipe:&lt;/i> to the left to open your bookmarks and to the right to open your readLater
        list. Swipe to top to close the app. This works everywhere.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Click (only in the browser):&lt;/i> you can enter a search term (see below) or a url. By pressing \"enter\" or
        the magnifier icon, the website will load.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Long click (only in the browser):&lt;/i> opens the tab preview (see below).&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>History (only in the browser):&lt;/i> opens a list of the last visited websites. Long pressing reloads the website.</string>

    <string name="help_tabs_title">&lt;b>Tab (preview):&lt;/b></string>
    <string name="help_tabs">
        To open a tab simply click on the preview. If you long press on a preview your favorite will open in this tab.
        The opened tab is highlighted. Clicking the close button resets the tab. You can swipe left and right to switch the tabs.</string>

    <string name="help_menu_title">&lt;b>Menu:&lt;/b></string>
    <string name="help_menu">
        &lt;i>Save website:&lt;/i> you can save the website to your bookmark, readLater or passStorage list or
        save a screenshot of the whole website.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Share website:&lt;/i> you can share the screenshot of a website, share the link as text or copy the link
        to the clipboard.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Search on site:&lt;/i> search for text on any website.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Open passStorage:&lt;/i> open your login data list.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Open download directory:&lt;/i> opens the download directory to show, share, rename or delete files.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Settings (popup dialog):&lt;/i> Here you can overwrite the default settings for a short time. These settings
        will get lost at the next app start. By clicking the red cross you can also add websites to a whitelist for javascript.
        They will be marked with a \"green check icon\". Javascript will then always be allowed for these websites (even after
        restarting the app). To open the main settings screen, click on \"Settings\" at the bottom of the popup dialog.&lt;br>&lt;br>
        &lt;i>Settings:&lt;/i> In the settings you can configure the behavior of the app, some privacy and
        security settings. At the app start these settings will always be loaded.</string>

    <string name="help_search_title">&lt;b>Search:&lt;/b></string>
    <string name="help_search">
        You can set your preferred search engine and the language for Wikipedia in the settings. You can search direct on different
        sites by clicking the list symbol right of the magnifier icon. The supported sites you can also configure in the settings.</string>


    //String arrays

    <string-array name="listArrayFont">
        <item>Small (70%)</item>
        <item>Normal (100%)</item>
        <item>Big (130%)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesFont">
        <item>70</item>
        <item>100</item>
        <item>130</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArraySearchEngine">
        <item>Duckduckgo</item>
        <item>Google</item>
        <item>Google (encrypted)</item>
        <item>MetaGer</item>
        <item>Startpage</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesSearchEngine">
        <item>https://duckduckgo.com/?q=</item>
        <item>https://www.google.com/search?&amp;q=</item>
        <item>https://encrypted.google.com/search?q=</item>
        <item>https://metager.de/meta/meta.ger3?focus=web&amp;eingabe=</item>
        <item>https://startpage.com/do/search?query=</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArrayWikiLang">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>German</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesWikiLang">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>de</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArrayOrientation">
        <item>Auto rotate (sensor)</item>
        <item>Auto rotate (device)</item>
        <item>Portrait</item>
        <item>Landscape</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesOrientation">
        <item>auto</item>
        <item>device</item>
        <item>portrait</item>
        <item>landscape</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArrayCookies">
        <item>Accept all cookies</item>
        <item>Accept all except 3. party cookies</item>
        <item>Accept no cookies</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesCookies">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArrayFull">
        <item>Hide statusbar</item>
        <item>Hide toolbar</item>
        <item>Hide both</item>
        <item>Hide nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesFull">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="def_wiki">en</string>
    <string name="def_search">https://duckduckgo.com/?q=</string>
    <string name="def_rot">device</string>

    <string-array name="listArrayTabMain">
        <item>Browser</item>
        <item>Bookmarks</item>
        <item>readLater</item>
        <item>History</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesTabMain">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArrayTheme">
        <item>Green (green|orange)</item>
        <item>Blue (blue|orange)</item>
        <item>Pink (pink|orange)</item>
        <item>Purple (purple|orange)</item>
        <item>Teal (teal|orange)</item>
        <item>Red (red|blue)</item>
        <item>Orange (orange|blue)</item>
        <item>Brown (brown|orange)</item>
        <item>Grey (grey|blue)</item>
        <item>Dark (grey|grey)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesTheme">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>