<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    //License Dialog

    <string name="about_title">Copyright © 2016  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        For more information visit the project site in github: https://github.com/scoute-dich/Browser&lt;br>&lt;br>

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Used open source projects:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>browser&lt;br>
        https://github.com/yoshihiroando/browser&lt;br>

        Android-ObservableScrollView&lt;br>
        https://github.com/ksoichiro/Android-ObservableScrollView&lt;/i>
    </string>


    //Help Dialog

    <string name="help_text">

        To exit the app you can just double click back in the browser. If you want, you can enable offline support in the settings.
        Websites will then be saved in the cache.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>The lists:&lt;/b>&lt;br>

        Every list has a context menu, which you can reach by long pressing an item. The readLater and history lists can be cleared
        with one click.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &#8226;&lt;i> Bookmark:&lt;/i> as always - save your favorite websites for a faster access.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> readLater:&lt;/i> here you can save websites if you want to read them anytime later, if they are not
        important enough to be a bookmark.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> History:&lt;/i> well, your browser history.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Toolbar (bottom):&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Click (also magnifier icon):&lt;/i> you can enter a search term (see below) or a url. By pressing \"enter\" or
        the magnifier icon, the website will load.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Long click:&lt;/i> will close the entire app (can be disabled in settings).&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Swipe:&lt;/i> to the left to open your bookmarks and to the right to open your readLater list.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> History:&lt;/i> opens a list of the last visited websites.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Menu:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Save website:&lt;/i> you can save the website to your bookmark or readLater list or save a screenshot of the
        whole website.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Share website:&lt;/i> you can share the screenshot of a website, share the link as text or copy the link
        to the clipboard.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Search on site:&lt;/i> search for text on any website.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Open downloads:&lt;/i> opens the system download manager.&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Settings:&lt;/i> In the settings you can configure the behavior of the app, some privacy and security
        settings.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Search:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        You can set your preferred search engine and the language for Wikipedia in the settings. You can search direct on different
        sites by typing the following before your search term (with the space):&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &#8226;&lt;i> Duckduckgo:&lt;/i> \".d \"&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Flickr (creative common license):&lt;/i> \".f \"&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Github:&lt;/i> \".g \"&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Google:&lt;/i> \".G \"&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> MetaGer:&lt;/i> \".m \"&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Startpage:&lt;/i> \".s \"&lt;br>
        &#8226;&lt;i> Wikipedia:&lt;/i> \".w \"
    </string>


    //String arrays

    <string-array name="listArrayFont">
        <item>Small (70%)</item>
        <item>Normal (100%)</item>
        <item>Big (130%)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesFont">
        <item>70</item>
        <item>100</item>
        <item>130</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArraySearchEngine">
        <item>Duckduckgo</item>
        <item>Google (if you REALLY want it …)</item>
        <item>MetaGer</item>
        <item>Startpage</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesSearchEngine">
        <item>https://duckduckgo.com/?q=</item>
        <item>https://www.google.com/search?&amp;q=</item>
        <item>https://metager.de/meta/meta.ger3?focus=web&amp;eingabe=</item>
        <item>https://startpage.com/do/search?query=</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listArrayWikiLang">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>German</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="listValuesWikiLang">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>de</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>