<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>

    <string name="changelog_title">Changelog</string>
    <string name="changelog_dialog">
        &lt;i>Project site: https://github.com/scoute-dich/Browser&lt;br>
        Changelog: https://github.com/scoute-dich/browser/blob/master/CHANGELOG.md&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Version: 5.7&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Please read the \"Help dialog\" for more information.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        \u25AA new: delete indexed databases and local web storage&lt;br>
        \u25AA new: Spanish translation (thanks to Herman Nunez)&lt;br>
        \u25AA new: confirmation dialog before making backup&lt;br>
        \u25AA new: delete separate lists&lt;br>
        \u25AA new: show unsecured connections and try reloading secure&lt;br>
        \u25AA new: search engines (Startpage DE, Searx)&lt;br>
        \u25AA new: notification when download or screenshot complete&lt;br>
        \u25AA ew: block remote content&lt;br>
        \u25AA improved Chinese translation (thanks: lishoujun)&lt;br>
        \u25AA removed: Snackbar (replaced with toasts)&lt;br>
        \u25AA removed: request desktop site&lt;br>
        \u25AA removed: build in file manager&lt;br>
        \u25AA fix: some strings (thanks: gr1sh)&lt;br>
        \u25AA fix: some urls opening search results
    </string>

    <string name="startpage_title">Startpage</string>
    <string name="startpage_dialog">Here you can access all your data: saved sites on the startpage, bookmarks, history, saved
        login data and the integrated file browser. In the settings you can decide which content will be shown at start.</string>

    <string name="fastToggle_title">Fast toggle</string>
    <string name="fastToggle_dialog">If you long press the \"menu\" or the \"Navigation button\" the \"Fast toggle dialog\"
        will open. Here you can change some important settings without leaving the current website. You can also add websites
        to your whitelist for AdBlocker, JavaScript or Cookies..</string>

    <string name="toolbar_title">Toolbar</string>
    <string name="toolbar_dialog">At the bottom of the screen you have the toolbar. You can enter URLs or search for
        something, reload the website and open the menu. Long click on the \"menu button\" to open the \"Fast toggle menu\".
        Swipe the toolbar up to open the tab preview. To switch between tabs swipe left or right.</string>

    <string name="tab_title">Tab preview</string>
    <string name="tab_dialog">Click the preview of a tab to select it, click again to close the tab preview. To close a tab simply
        swipe to preview to the top or bottom.</string>

    <string name="menu_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="menu_dialog">Manage your tabs, share or save content, handle the current tab or use some features: just try it.
        The menu can be dismissed, like all other notifications, by clicking back, clicking outside the menu or simply be
        swiping the menu down.</string>

    <string name="not_title">Notifications</string>
    <string name="not_dialog">Notifications are displayed on the bottom of the screen. They can also be dismissed like the
        menus.</string>

    <string name="nav_title">Navigation</string>
    <string name="nav_dialog">Use the \"Navigation Button\": swipe up/down -> scroll to top/bottom;
    swipe left/right -> navigate back/forward; click -> open the menu; long click -> open \"Fast toggle dialog\";
        double click -> Hide the \"Navigation Button\".</string>

    <string name="settings_dialog">There are even more options in the settings. Try it out!</string>


    <string name="license_title">Copyright © 2017  by Gaukler Faun</string>
    <string name="license_dialog">
        &lt;i>For more information visit the project site on Github: https://github.com/scoute-dich/Browser&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
        it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
        the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
        (at your option) any later version.

        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
        GNU General Public License for more details.

        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
        along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;i>Following open source libraries or projects are used within this software:&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Android Sliding Up Panel&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        Umano: News Read To You&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vUruG&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Android Swipe-to-Dismiss&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        Roman Nurik&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vUruO&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>DynamicGrid&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        askerov&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vTHZH&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Lightning Browser&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Mozilla Public License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        Anthony Restaino&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vUruk&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Material Design Icons&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1.&lt;br>
        Templarian&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/Templarian/MaterialDesign&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Ninja&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        Matthew Lee&lt;br>
        &lt;i>http://git.io/vUrEh&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>SimpleEncryptionLib&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        Apache License Version 2.0&lt;br>
        hummatli&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/hummatli/SimpleEncryptionLib</string>

    <string name="cont_dialog">
        &lt;i>First I would like to thank all people who contributed in any way on this project. They submitted issues,
        translated or helped in any other way. On following sites you can become a active member of this
        great community:&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>XDA-thread:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        XDA is a great community for developers and smartphone enthusiasts. Here you can report issues, ask for new features
        and everything other related to \"FOSS Browser\".&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://forum.xda-developers.com/android/apps-games/app-browser-t3500091&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Github:&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        On Github you can see the source code of \"FOSS Browser\". This is the more technical solution: open issues, ask for new
        features or even help developing or translating.&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/scoute-dich/browser&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;br>


        &lt;i>Following people contributed at this project. If I have forgotten anybody, please contact me:&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Gaukler Faun&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA Main developer and initiator of this project.&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/scoute-dich&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>CGSLURP LLC&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA Helped to implement AdBlock and \"request desktop site\" in the previous version of \"FOSS Browser\".&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/futrDevelopment&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>element54&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA fix: keyboard problems (issue #105).&lt;br>
        \u25AA new: option to disable confirmation dialogs on exit&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/element54&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>gr1sh&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA fix: some German strings (issues #124, #131).&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/gr1sh&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Herman Nunez&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA Spanish translation&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/junior012&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Jumping Yang&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA Chinese translation in the previous version of \"FOSS Browser\".&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/JumpingYang001&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>lishoujun&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA Chinese translation&lt;br>
        \u25AA bug hunting&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/lishoujun&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>Secangkir Kopi&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA Indonesian translation&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/Secangkir-Kopi&lt;/i>&lt;br>&lt;br>

        &lt;b>splinet&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        \u25AA Russian translation in the previous version of \"FOSS Browser\".&lt;br>
        &lt;i>https://github.com/splinet&lt;/i>

    </string>

</resources>
